<div class="container-fluid" xmlns:t="http://twistedmatrix.com/ns/twisted.web.template/0.1">
    <h2>Frequenty Asked Questions</h2>
    <p><b>Who should use this?</b></p>
    <p>If you are someone looking for an easy way promote yourself via Twitter Sphere.</p>
    <p>If you are someone looking to monetize your a twitter account.</p>

    <p><b>How does this work?</b></p>
    <p>If you are looking to promote we connect you to users who want to spread the word about your business.</p>
    <p>If you are looking to earn we connect you to users who are seeking promotion.</p>

    <p><b>How do I promote my service?</b></p>
    <p>There also two ways to do this.</p>
    <p>The first way requires you to create an open ask order. This order will indicate to our users that you are seeking to relay one of your tweets to their audience. Once the order is created a portion of your balance is allocated to the pay the user who is advertizing for you.</p>

    <p>The second way requires you to work with users who've identified themselves as active promoters. You can find these users in the bids section of the market. Before you invest in any of them you can review the kind of audience they are working with and help you make get the best value for your money.</p>

    <p><b>How do I earn?</b></p>
    <p>There are two ways to do this.</p>
    <p>The first way requires you to fullfil an open ask order. The idea is this. A user who wants to advertize via your twitter timeline maintains a balance on the site. A portion of that balance goes to you once you fullfil several retweet requirements. For the first requirement you must retweet what the wants you to promote. For the second requirement you must maintain the tweet in the retweeted state for at least 48 hours. After the 48 hour period you must return to the site and claim you earnings.</p>
    <p>The second way requires you to list yourself as an active promoter. To do this you must create an open bid order where you indicate what you are seeking to charge per tweet and what you audience is like.</p>

    <p><b>How do I get started?</b></p>
    <p>To get started, you must register on the site, have a twitter account and a valid bitcoin address.</p>

    <p><b>What is my market score?</b></p>
    <p>The market score allows users who want to promote their service determine a reasonable price for their advertizing campaign.</p>
    <p>The market score also allows users who want to earn money estimate their potential earnings.</p>
</div>
